the time of trouble such as never was
Came Upon the world as an overwhelming
surprise watching the replay of Earth's
final scene in the courtroom is
emotional for us on many different
levels the redeemed jurors at last get
to see the ripening and end result of
the principles of Satan's Rebellion
which began in heaven the deception had
been so deeply laid the plot so
perfectly calculated that it exposed
with Clarity all who had not truly
submitted themselves to the will and
truth of God the witnesses who now take
the stand are those who lived through it
or had Faithfully given their lives
during this final Conflict the final
events of Earth's history began to
unfold simultaneously with the going
forth of the fully restored
unadulterated gospel the churches that
had ultimately rejected the preaching of
this message became designated as
Babylon Revelation 148 and as the Beast
that had horns like a lamb but spoke
like a dragon Revelation
13:1 these symbols appointed to those
who profess to follow the lamb but in
actuality espoused the lawlessness of
the Dragon Satan had crafted a slow and
deliberate process of leading the
churches of Earth to focus more and more
on an Earthly nationalism and less and
less of the Heavenly Kingdom the
churches in the most powerful Nation on
Earth began to desire forcing
Christianity on society in the name of
Jesus of course they thought they were
doing God's service but because they did
not know Jesus they did not understand
that love and righteousness cannot be
forced the ones who had been bent on
this idea of Earthly dominionism
revealed the Same Heart Lucifer had in
heaven the desire to rule by force in
the name and under the guise of
Holiness yet thousands of unbelievers
revolted against any such idea of making
the world a Christian theocracy Skeptics
atheists and people from other religions
United in opposing this false movement
within Christianity to convert the world
through legislation they saw this as a
mere repeat and image to the Church of
the dark Ages which had done that exact
thing using political power to persuade
the masses to serve God many of God's
people students of prophecy throughout
the ages had known that the Bible
prophesied that the entire world would
unite against the people of God we knew
this was called the time of trouble
Daniel
121:2 what many of us could not
understand was how a world so divided in
beliefs would ultimately unite to fight
against those who keep the Commandments
of God and have the faith of Jesus
Revelation
12:17 those of us not living in these
final days find out here in the court
exactly what or rather exactly who was
able to unite Skeptics religionists of
all kinds with Babylon the system of
Fallen churches across the globe it was
in fact Satan counterfeiting the
appearing of Christ the day it happened
took the World by surprise the Fallen
Christian churches who had embraced
false teachings were not aware that when
Christ returned the second time it would
neither be secret nor invisible ible
Matthew
24:27 they did not know that when Jesus
came again his feet would not touch the
ground but instead he would stop in the
air and call the Saints up to meet him
in the sky taking them with him to
heaven for a thousand years 1
Thessalonians 4:13-17 Revelation 20:4
and 5 John
141:3 thus when Satan appeared as a
being of light pretending to be Christ
at his second coming 2 Thessalonians 2:4
while his feet touched the Earth
claiming to set up the millennial
Kingdom on Earth the unstudied Christian
Church received him as Jesus he had now
accomplished on Earth what he attempted
in heaven to be worshiped as the most
high Isaiah
14:12 but he did not come alone when
Jesus returns the dead are raised to
life so to complete this masterpiece of
deception Satan's Fallen Angels
impersonate the dead Revelation
16:13 this overwhelming miracle
convinces even the skeptic The Atheist
the stubborn unbeliever who swore they
would never believe unless they saw now
seeing is believing and the entire world
Muslims atheists Fallen Christianity
Jews Buddhists agnostics and everyone in
between bow at the foot of this
counterfeit Messiah because the
Christian churches were led to believe
that the 1,000-year rule would take
place on this Earth they were ripe for
the ultimate deception of Satan
pretending to be Christ and ushering in
this period
this impostor tells them that the sign
of allegiance to his Millennial Kingdom
on Earth is the Sabbath and that from
one new moon to another and from one
Sabbath to another All Flesh is to come
before him to worship Isaiah 66:12 and
13 by this however he means the first
day of the week instead of the seventh
day this is his attempt to lead the
whole world to worship him as the
Creator through observing a false
Sabbath in dedication to himself those
who refuse him who see through this
charade are they that keep the
Commandments of God and have the faith
of Jesus they know this is a counterfeit
and in saying this they incur the Wrath
and vitriol of his deceived Believers as
if they are blaspheming Christ himself
this false Jesus then tells the masses
that those who refuse to obey him are
Blasphemous and are worthy of death and
should not be privileged to buy or sell
Revelation 13:15 to1 17 he tells them
that these are the wicked ones whom are
to be judged during the 1,000 years on
Earth and peace comes only as these
rebellious ones are eliminated how
powerful a deception he leads the wicked
to think they were the righteous ones
who would judge on Earth and just as the
decree to kill those who refuse to
worship the beast in His image or
receive the mark of this Antichrist it
was then that I who had been dead for
over 200 years heard the words awake
awake